Find someone made just for you.
Companion is a horror, thriller, science fiction film directed by Drew Hancock.
During a weekend getaway at a secluded lakeside estate, a group of friends finds
themselves entangled in a web of secrets, deception, and advanced technology.
As tensions rise and loyalties are tested, they uncover unsettling
truths about themselves and the world around them.
Iris, played by Sophie Thatcher.
Josh, played by Jack Quaid.
Patrick, played by Lukas Gage.
Kat, played by Megan Suri.
Eli, played by Harvey Guillén.
Sergey, played by Rupert Friend.
Companion is a 2025 American science fiction thriller film written and
directed by Drew Hancock, in his directorial debut.
It was produced by Zach Cregger, Roy Lee, Raphael Margules, and J.
Sophie Thatcher and Jack Quaid star as a couple on a weekend getaway with friends at a remote cabin,
which unravels into chaos after a revelation that one of the guests is a companion robot.
Companion was released in the United States by Warner Bros.
Pictures on January 31, 2025.
The film received positive reviews from critics and grossed
$36.7 million on a budget of $10 million.
The film explores themes of android, artificial intelligence
(a.i.), cabin, robot, boyfriend girlfriend relationship.
The tone is lighthearted and dark and uplifting.